[
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of autonoetic? How would you use it in a sentence?",
        "answer": "autonoetic.md",
        "correct_attempts": 3,
        "total_attempts": 3,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00001"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of sen qa non? How would you use it in a sentence?",
        "answer": "sine qua non.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00002"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of 'modus operandi'? How would you use it in a sentence?",
        "answer": "modus operandi.md",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00003"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of zeitgeist? How would you use it in a sentence?",
        "answer": "zeitgeist.md",
        "correct_attempts": 2,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00004"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of Ontogeny? How would you use it in a sentence?",
        "answer": "ontogeny.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 4,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00005"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of Taxonomy? How would you use it in a sentence?",
        "answer": "taxonomy.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 2,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00006"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of conflated?",
        "answer": "The definition of conflated is to combine two or more things into one. An example of conflated is a restaurant that serves both Chinese and Japanese food.",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00007"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does implicit and explicit mean?",
        "answer": "Implicit means implied or understood though not plainly or directly expressed. Explicit means stated clearly and in detail, leaving no room for confusion or doubt.",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00008"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of Aplysia?",
        "answer": "Aplysia is a genus of medium-sized to extremely large sea slugs, specifically sea hares, which are one clade of large sea slugs, marine gastropod mollusks.",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00009"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of impinge?",
        "answer": "Impinge means to have an effect, especially a negative one.",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00010"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of labile?",
        "answer": "Labile means liable to change; easily altered.",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00011"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does epigenetic mean?",
        "answer": "Epigenetic means relating to or arising from non-genetic influences on gene expression.",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00012"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does dileneate mean?",
        "answer": "Delineate means to describe or portray (something) precisely.",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 0,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00013"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of provisionally?",
        "answer": "Provisionally means for the present; temporarily.",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00014"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of eclectic?",
        "answer": "eclectic.md",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 0,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00015"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of isomorphic?",
        "answer": "isomorphic.md",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00016"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of colloquially?",
        "answer": "colloquially.md",
        "correct_attempts": 1,
        "total_attempts": 1,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00017"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of putative?",
        "answer": "putative.md",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 0,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00018"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does concomitant mean?",
        "answer": "concomitant.md",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 0,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00019"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does heterogenous mean?",
        "answer": "heterogenous.md",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 0,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00020"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does differential mean?",
        "answer": "differential.md",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 0,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00021"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the definition of juxtaposition?",
        "answer": "juxtaposition.md",
        "correct_attempts": 0,
        "total_attempts": 0,
        "unique_id": "dictionary00022"
    }
]